If you are watching this video, it's because you want to improve the appearance of your breasts,
perhaps because you want to increase the size, improve the projection or maybe because you
have lost volume and they have fallen and you want to recover the appearance before
breastfeeding or when you were younger. Maybe it is the opposite and you have a very large
and heavy breast that causes you discomfort and pain and you want to reduce its size.
Regardless of your case, through a breast augmentation, breast lift or breast reduction
procedure we can give you the result you dreamed of, the result that allows you to feel good
about yourself, that allows you to wear the clothes you want and not the ones that you
have to wear. The result that makes you feel confident, wherever you are, no matter if it is
a family dinner, if you are at work or wearing a swimsuit. Let me introduce myself, I'm Dr.
Fulvio Correa, a board certified plastic surgeon. For more than 10 years, I have helped women
of different ages to achieve their breast dream, for example Andrea, who now has fuller
and more projected breasts and share with us these incredible photos that you are seeing right now
or Camila, who send us these photos of her magnificent breast lift result. Just like them,
I can also help you to achieve a result like the ones you just watched. But that's not the
best part. Through our all-inclusive program that we have designed specifically for
patients who come from other countries like you, my staff will accompany you in every phase
of the journey, answering all your questions, helping you to plan your trip, scheduling your
accommodation in our recovery house, where you will have all the comforts and care necessary
for a prompt and satisfactory recovery. Schedule your free evaluation right now,
and start your journey to achieve your goals and boost your confidence.